(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{1:function(e,a,n){},10:function(e,a,n){e.exports=n(15)},15:function(e,a,n){"use strict";n.r(a);var t=n(4),s=n(5),o=n(8),i=n(6),r=n(9),u=n(0),l=n.n(u),c=n(7),m=n.n(c),v=(n(1),[{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0991099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0999989"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"97675678"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}]),h=[{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0991099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0999989"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"97675678"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}],d=[{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0991099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0999989"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"97675678"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","nammo","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}],p=function(e){return console.log(e),"easy"===e?function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return v.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e)}():"medium"===e?function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return d.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e)}():function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return h.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e)}()},y=n(2),k=function(e){var a=e.question,n=e.options,t=e.selected,s=Object(u.useState)(n),o=Object(y.a)(s,2),i=o[0],r=o[1];return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionBox"},l.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},a),i.map((function(e,a){return l.a.createElement("button",{key:a,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){r([e]),t(e)}}," ",e)})))},q=function(e){var a=e.selectedLevel;return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"levelBox"},l.a.createElement("button",{className:"level",onClick:function(){return a("easy")}},"easy"),l.a.createElement("button",{className:"level",onClick:function(){return a("medium")}},"medium"),l.a.createElement("button",{className:"level",onClick:function(){return a("hard")}},"hard"))},w=function(e){var a=e.selectUserName,n=Object(u.useState)(""),t=Object(y.a)(n,2),s=t[0],o=t[1];return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"inputBox"},l.a.createElement("input",{type:"text",onChange:function(e){return o(e.target.value)},value:s,className:"input",placeholder:"enter your name"}),l.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn",onClick:function(){return a(s)}},"Enter"))},b=["Very Poor","Poor","Bad","Good","Strong","Very Strong"],I=function(e){var a=e.score,n=e.playAgain,t=e.name;return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},l.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},l.a.createElement("b",null," ",t," ")," you are ",l.a.createElement("b",null," ",b[a]," "),", you have"," ",l.a.createElement("b",null,a),"/ 5 correct answer ! ! !"),l.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:n},"Play Again"))},f=function(e){function a(){var e;return Object(t.a)(this,a),(e=Object(o.a)(this,Object(i.a)(a).call(this))).getQuestions=function(e){return p(e)},e.selectUserName=function(a){e.setState({name:a})},e.selectedLevel=function(a){e.setState({level:a,questionBank:e.getQuestions(a)})},e.playAgain=function(){e.setState({score:0,count:0,level:"",responses:0})},e.computeAnswer=function(a,n){a===n&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<5?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.timer=function(){var a=e.state.count+1;a<=4&&e.setState({count:a})},e.timerVar=null,e.state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0,count:0,level:"",name:""},e}return Object(r.a)(a,e),Object(s.a)(a,[{key:"componentDidUpdate",value:function(){""!==this.state.name&&""!==this.state.level&&0===this.state.count&&(this.timerVar=setInterval(this.timer,1e3))}},{key:"componentWillUnmount",value:function(){clearTimeout(this.timerVar)}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},l.a.createElement("div",{className:"title"},"QuizOn"),""===this.state.name?l.a.createElement(w,{selectUserName:this.selectUserName}):null,""!==this.state.name&&""!==this.state.level&&this.state.count<=3?l.a.createElement("div",{className:"levelLable"},l.a.createElement("b",null,"Name :"),this.state.name,"\xa0\xa0\xa0",l.a.createElement("b",null,"Level :"),this.state.level,l.a.createElement("div",{className:"timer"},this.state.count),l.a.createElement("hr",null)):null,""!==this.state.name&&""===this.state.level?l.a.createElement(q,{selectedLevel:this.selectedLevel}):null,""!==this.state.name&&""!==this.state.level&&this.state.count<=3&&this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(a){var n=a.question,t=a.answers,s=a.correct,o=a.questionId;return l.a.createElement(k,{question:n,options:t,key:o,selected:function(a){return e.computeAnswer(a,s)}})})),""!==this.state.name&&5===this.state.responses||this.state.count>3?l.a.createElement(I,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain,name:this.state.name}):null)}}]),a}(u.Component);m.a.render(l.a.createElement(f,null),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[10,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.bb07046e.chunk.js.map